Finding Aid for Michigan Daily Records, 1950-2006
Bentley Historical Library
- Negatives-Topical, 1968-1982; 3.5 linear feet
  - D-G
    - Ford, Gerald, 1936-1978; 22 envelopes
      - With Japanese ambassador, November 4, 1977 (Box 22)
      - At Griffin Conference at the Hyatt in Dearborn, September 25, 1978 (Box 22)
      - At Dearborn, November, 1978 (Box 22)
      - May 12, 1981 (Box 22)
    - Ford Library, September 17, 1981 (Box 22)
    - Forsyth, Ilene (Professor of History of Art) (Box 22)
    - Fotjik, Kathleen (Box 22)
    - Fowles, John (Box 22)
      (See-Ehrlichman, John)
    - Fox, Dan, September 16, 1971 (Box 22)
    - Fox, Dr., February 8, 1978 (Box 22)
    - Foye, Laurence, August 18, 1975 (Box 22)
    - Freeman, Chico (musician), September 27, 1980 (Box 22)
    - Freeman (Box 22)
    - Freidman, Monroe, March 20 and 23, 1978; 2 envelopes (Box 22)
    - Friars (musical group), March 29, 1980 (Box 22)
    - Fricke, Benno, March 26, 1975 (Box 22)
    - Friedan, Betty (writer, feminist activist), September 30, 1975 (Box 22)
    - Frieder, Bill, February 17, 1975 (Box 22)
    - Fromm, Lynnette, September 11, 1975 (Box 22)
    - Frye, Billy (University Dean), 1977; 1980; 5 envelopes (Box 22)
    - Fusfeld, Daniel (Box 22)
      (See-Ackley, Iran seminar)
    - Future Worlds (lecture series), 1974-1975; 3 envelopes (Box 22)
    - Galvin, Alexander (Box 22)
    - Gardner, Sam, Detroit judge, February 15, 1978 (Box 22)
    - Garland, Dick, Minority Services, July 10, 1973; May 22, 1978; 2 envelopes (Box 22)
    - Garris, March 30, 1971 (Box 22)
    - Garry, Charles, March 19, 1979 (Box 22)
    - Gaskell, Jerry (Box 22)
    - Gaskin, Steven (Box 22)
    - Gellic, John, January 28, 1981 (Box 22)
    - Geness, Linda, February 1, 1971 (Box 22)
    - Geography, University of Michigan Department of, March and June, 1981; 2 envelopes (Box 22)
    - Geralds (Box 22)
    - Gibson, Judy, February 15, 1975 (Box 22)
    - Gill, Lee, 1973; 3 envelopes (Box 22)
    - Ginger, Ann Fagen (?), December 9, 1972 (Box 22)
    - Gingrich, Arnold (Box 22)
    - Ginsberg, Allen, 1977-1978; 3 envelopes (Box 22)
    - Girl Scouts, Adult, February 28, 1980 (Box 22)
    - Giroud, Françoise, April 30, 1976; 4 envelopes (Box 22)
    - Glee Club, November 1979; 2 envelopes (Box 22)
    - Goeman, Dorothy ("Native American"), August 5, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Goldwater, Barry (Box 22)
    - Gonzales, Corky, January 13, 1979 (Box 22)
    - Good, Sandra, September 11, 1975 (Box 22)
    - Goodman (Box 22)
    - Goodman, Deb, 1975 (Box 22)
    - Goodyear Blimp, September 21, 1979 (Box 22)
    - Gordos (professor), April 11, 1972 (Box 22)
    - Graduate Employees Organization (GEO), 1979; 1981; 2 envelopes (Box 22)
    - Graduation, 4 envelopes
      - Harold Shapiro speaker, May 1, 1981 (Box 22)
      - Medical School graduation, June 1981; June 4, 1982; 2 envelopes (Box 22)
        (See also-Welby, Marcus)
      - South African apartheid protest (Box 22)
    - Graf, Karen (Republican city council candidate) (Box 22)
    - Graf, Otto, October 9, 1978 (Box 22)
    - Graham ("Pylan's manager") (Box 22)
    - Grant workshop, October 11, 1979 (Box 22)
    - Gravel, Mike (Senator), October 29, 1972; January 23, 1978; 2 envelopes (Box 22)
    - Gray, Pat (Box 22)
    - Greek system, 3 envelopes
      - Rush, September 28, 1979 (Box 22)
      - Mud Bowl, November 20, 1980 (Box 22)
      - Theta Zi co-ed fraternity, September 11, 1981 (Box 22)
    - Green (professor) (Box 22)
    - Greenburg and Allan (council candidates), January 18, 1978 (Box 22)
    - Greene, Earl, February 18, 1980 (Box 22)
    - Greene, Gael, January 16, 1978 (Box 22)
    - Greene, Marc (2nd ward candidate), January 30, 1978 (Box 22)
    - Gregory, Dick, October 16, 1978 (Box 22)
    - Grew, Raymond (Box 22)
    - Gribbs, Roman (Detroit mayor), April 12, 1972 (Box 22)
    - Griffen (Box 22)
    - Griffen, Arleen (Box 22)
    - Griffin, Robert, Senator, February 13, 1978 (Box 22)
    - Griffiths, Martha (member of U.S. Congress from Michigan), November 28, 1977; undated; 2 envelopes (Box 22)
    - Groppi, Father, October 13, 1971 (Box 22)
    - Grotian, Harvey (financial aid director), January 27, 1982 (Box 22)
    - Gruening, Ernest, Senator (Box 22)
    - Gumbleton, Bishop, October 23, 1980 (Box 22)
    - Guttman, March 24, 1978 (Box 22)
  - H-L
    - HUA, 1976 (Box 22)
    - Haber, Al, March 24, 1978 (Box 22)
    - Hadler (council member), March 31, 1973 (Box 22)
    - Hagan (Box 22)
    - Haldeman, H. R. (Box 22)
    - Half-way house (West William Street). (Box 22)
      (See "Gellic, John.")
    - Hall, Donald (poet), April 4, 1973; March 16, 1978; 2 envelopes (Box 22)
    - Hall, Gus, September 23, 1976; 3 envelopes (Box 22)
    - Hall, Harris (Box 22)
      (See-Shapiro, Harold)
    - Halpern, October 20, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Halpert, Barbara (Box 22)
    - Hamilton, Charles, January 27, 1970 (Box 22)
    - Handicapped person (Box 22)
    - Hants and Ludwig (5th ward), February 18, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Harburg, Ernie, February 22, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Harks, Judith (5th ward city council candidate), March 24, 1976 (Box 22)
    - Harrington, Mike (Box 22)
    - Harris, Allan (Box 22)
    - Harris, David (Box 22)
    - Harris, Fred, September 15, 1975 (Box 22)
    - Harris, Robert, Mayor, 1970-71, 3 envelopes
      - January 7, 1970 (Box 22)
      - Mayoral debate, February 23, 1971 (Box 22)
      - Harris, Garris, Cornell, debate at Daily, March 14, 1971 (Box 22)
    - Harrison, George, October 23, 1974 (Box 22)
    - Harrison, T. H (Box 22)
    - Hart, Jane, at Hill Auditorium, October 6, 1970 (Box 22)
    - Hart, Phil (Senator), 1969-74, 4 envelopes
      - February 21, 1969 (Box 22)
      - February 12, 1970 (Box 22)
      - With Sandor Levin, February 25, 1972 (Box 22)
      - With Peter Eckstein at East Quad, October 28, 1974 (Box 22)
    - Hartman, John (University Hospital psychologist), January 16, 1974 (Box 22)
    - Harvey, Douglas (Sheriff), January 7, 1970; undated; 2 envelopes (Box 22)
    - Hash Bash, April 1, 1980 (Box 22)
    - Hatcher, Harlan, October 26, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Hatcher, Richard (mayor of Gary, Indiana), February 21, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Hawkes, John, January 19, 1976 (Box 22)
    - Hayden, Tom, October 29, 1970; January 19, 1976; 2 envelopes (Box 22)
    - Hayes, Ed, February 2, 1972 (Box 22)
    - Hayes, William (Box 22)
    - Heardman, Pirsilla (?), at The Ark, February 3, 1978 (Box 22)
    - Hefner, Bob, May 20, 1971 (Box 22)
    - Hefner, Keith, January 24, 1978 (Box 22)
    - Hegyi, Dennis (Physics professor), November 16, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Helicopter, April 10, 1979 (Box 22)
    - Heller, J., January 15, 1975; 2 envelopes (Box 22)
    - Hemeryck (4th ward council candidate), February 16, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Henry, Robert (Republican) (Box 22)
    - Hess, Carl, September 8, 1975 (Box 22)
    - Heynes, Roger (Box 22)
    - Hiking (Box 22)
      (See-Continental Divide hikers)
    - Hoffa, Jimmy, September 29, 1972; 1975; 2 envelopes (Box 22)
    - Holland and... (?)(musicians), January 29, 1980 (Box 22)
    - Holmes, William (Box 22)
      (See-Gellic, John)
    - Holt, John, April 4, 1975 (Box 22)
    - Homecoming, 1979; undated; 3 envelopes (Box 22)
    - Hood and Townridge, January 29, 1979 (Box 22)
    - Hook, Steve, July 9, 1981 (Box 22)
    - Hopwood awards, January 16, 1980 (Box 22)
    - Hornback, Bert (professor of English), April 9, 1975 (Box 22)
    - Hornstein, David, December 1972 (Box 22)
    - Horowitz, Vladimir (pianist), October 9, 1978 (Box 22)
    - Hospitals and health care, 1979-1982; 8 envelopes (Box 22)
      (See also-Mott)
    - House inspection, March 11, 1980 (Box 22)
    - Houseman, John, February 14, 1974 (Box 22)
    - Housing, April and June, 1982; 2 envelopes (Box 22)
    - Housing Conference (Box 22)
      (See-Equal Rights Amendment Walkathon)
    - Howe, Gordie (Detroit Red Wings ice hockey player) (Box 22)
    - Howard, Harry (Superintendent of Ann Arbor schools), November 16, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Hubbard, Phil (Box 22)
    - Huff, Rebecca (memorial service), September 18, 1980 (Box 22)
    - Huggins, Erica, March 19, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Hughes, Robert (Housing Director), October 27, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Hughes, Ted (poet, author) (Box 22)
    - Human Rights Party, 1972; undated; 2 envelopes (Box 22)
    - Human Sexual Response (band) (Box 22)
    - Humblees Frisbee Team, March 3, 1977; 3 envelopes (Box 22)
    - Humphrey, Hubert (Senator from Minnesota), 2 envelopes (Box 22)
    - Hunt, Linda, February 1, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Hunter, Martha (New York Times reporter), March 13, 1974 (Box 22)
    - Hunter, Robert, April 6, 1971 (Box 22)
    - Hyman, Gene (?) ("Tony the Tiger"), March 4, 1976 (Box 22)
    - Hymans, Saul (professor of economics and statistics) (Box 22)
    - Impact Dance, March and April, 1981; 2 envelopes (Box 22)
    - Institute for Social Research (Box 22)
      (See-Bluestone, Irving)
    - Interlochen, July 21, 1980 (Box 22)
    - Iran seminar, January 17, 1980 (Box 22)
    - Irish, Colonel (ROTC), November 1972 (Box 22)
    - Israel ("editorial interview"), February 2, 1982 (Box 22)
    - Israeli Dance (Box 22)
      (See-Michigan Student Assembly)
    - Isreal, David, October 6, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Jackson, David and Ethyl (Box 22)
    - Jacobs (SGC President), March 24, 1972 (Box 22)
    - Jazzfest, September 30, 1979 (Box 22)
    - Jemms, Linda, October 15, 1974 (Box 22)
    - Jenkins, Jango (leading "parade"), October 30, 1981 (Box 22)
    - Ji, Guru Maharaj (Box 22)
    - Johnson, Henry (professor and Vice President of Student Affairs), April 11, 1972; February 22, 1974; undated; 3 envelopes (Box 22)
    - Johnson, Lemuel (poet), November 6, 1973 (Box 22)
    - Johnson, Lloyd, January 29, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B. (students' reactions to Johnson's announcement that he will not run for office), March 31, 1968 (Box 22)
    - Johnson, Nicholas, FCC (Box 22)
    - Jones, Carol (Box 22)
    - Jones, James Earl, October 5, 1971 (Box 22)
    - Jones, LeRoi (Box 22)
    - Jong, Erica, February 1974; 2 envelopes (Box 22)
    - Jordan, Sherril, November 20,., 1980 (Box 22)
    - Justice, Charlie, February 21, 1974 (Box 22)
    - Kahn, Bruce (Box 22)
    - Kambley, Dr. ("walking into pre-trial exam"), December 11, 1974 (Box 22)
    - Kaminski, Stan, October 1, 1974 (Box 22)
    - Kamisar, Yale (professor of law), March 19, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Kaplan, Stanley, December 5, 1980 (Box 22)
      (See also-Greek system)
    - Karpinski, Ray (Box 22)
    - Kasmanski ("Ohio State Victory Day") (Box 22)
    - Katroshinko, Cathy, February 27, 1974 (Box 22)
    - Keitel, Harvey (Box 22)
      (See-Pryor, Richard)
    - Kellerman, Scott, October 17, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Kelley, Leo, Jr. (on trial), May-August 1981; 5 envelopes (Box 22)
    - Kelley, Frank, (state Attorney General), 1971; 1974; 2 envelopes (Box 22)
    - Kennedy, Florence, February 4, 1971 (Box 22)
    - Kennedy, Richard (Vice President for State Relations and Secretary of the University), September 15, 1971 (Box 22)
    - Kenworthy, Jamie (Ann Arbor councilman; in library interview with Krupa), February 3, 1978 (Box 22)
    - Kevorkin, Harry, February 6, 1974 (Box 22)
    - Kidd, Charles (Box 22)
    - King, Jean (attorney), December 2, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Kirberg (Box 22)
    - Kirscht, Jack, March 27, 1972 (Box 22)
    - Kish, George (professor of geography), 1971; 1981; 2 envelopes (Box 22)
    - Kissinger, Henry, August 3, 1977; undated; 2 envelopes (Box 22)
    - Klempner (Box 22)
    - Kolossos strike, June 15, 1981 (Box 22)
    - Knauss, Robert (Vice President for Student Affairs), September 15, 1970; May 20, 1971; 2 envelopes (Box 22)
    - Knot (Box 22)
      (See-Power, Sarah)
    - Koerner (?), John (Box 22)
    - Koeskin (?), February 14, 1972 (Box 22)
    - Kofzhavin (?), poet, April 16, 1974 (Box 22)
    - Kohn, Howard, November 21, 1970 (Box 22)
    - Kosinsky (Box 22)
    - Koster, Don, September 28, 1970; undated; 2 envelopes (Box 22)
    - Kraftowitz, Bob (Box 22)
    - Krasny, Walter (Ann Arbor Police Chief), 1970-1979; 5 envelopes (Box 22)
    - Kuhn, Maggie (Grey Panthers Party), October 1, 1980 (Box 22)
    - Kunstler, William (attorney), undated; 3 envelopes (Box 22)
    - Ky (South Vietnam) (Box 22)
    - Labor Conference, January 19, 1980 (Box 22)
    - Laing, Cheryl (Box 22)
      (See-Blood donation)
    - Lake, Oliver, October 6, 1983 (Box 22)
    - Landa, Boris, July 18, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Lansing, S. (Box 22)
      (See-Steinem, Gloria)
    - Lapham (Harper's editor) (Box 22)
      (See-Hopwood awards)
    - Lapides, Dr., February 16, 1982 (Box 22)
    - Lappe, Francis Moore ("Diet for a Small Planet"), October 7, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Latta, Ken, April 4, 1974; February 16, 1977; 2 envelopes (Box 22)
    - Law School
      - Library, August and October, 1981; 2 envelopes (Box 22)
        (See also-Ebony
      - Speaker, November 19, 1981 (Box 22)
    - Lawyers' Club (including races), 1980-1981; 3 envelopes (Box 22)
    - Lax, Gerald (City Prosecutor), September 14, 1971 (Box 22)
    - Lee, Dennis (medical illustrator), November 17, 1976 (Box 22)
    - Lee, Justine (Burger King manager), April 16, 1975 (Box 22)
    - Leiskow, Kathy (first woman battalion leader), October 9, 1979 (Box 22)
    - Letelier, Isabelle (Box 22)
      (See-Student Life--Teach-ins)
    - Levin, Sandor (Democratic politician), (?), 1974-1979; 4 envelopes
      (See also-Hart, Phil)
      - Campaign for Governor, February 27, 1974 (Box 22)
      - Campaign for Senate, October 6, 1978; 2 envelopes (Box 22)
      - At Law Quad, April 14, 1979 (Box 22)
    - Lewis, Eric, September 19, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Lewis, Jerry Lee (Box 22)
    - Lieberman, Lawrence (poetry reading), February 1, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Lindemer, Lawrence (Regent) (Box 22)
    - Livermore, Shaw (professor of History), March 4, 1976 (Box 22)
    - Lockwood, Ted, January 30, 1978 (Box 22)
    - Loggins, Kenny, October 16, 1979 (Box 22)
    - Loken, Newt (diving coach), October 11, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Long, Lance, October 27, 1979 (Box 22)
    - Longone, Jan (Box 22)
    - Lorenzo (reporter) (Box 22)
    - Losh, Hazel (astronomy professor), September 14, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Love/Lovejoy, Sam (environmentalist), February 8, 9, and 28, 1977; 3 envelopes (Box 22)
    - Luce, Don, February 25, 1974 (Box 22)
    - Lucker/Luker (?) (MSA), 1976; undated; 2 envelopes (Box 22)
    - Ludwig (5th ward) (Box 22)
      (See-Hants)
    - Ludwig, Guy, November 9, 1974 (Box 22)
    - Luther, Allin (professor of Persian Studies and Near East Studies), September 23, 1980 (Box 22)
  - M-O
    - McAllister, Sister (Box 22)
    - McBride, Owen, 1976-1978; 3 envelopes (Box 22)
    - McCabe, Irene, February 14, 1973 (Box 22)
    - McCarthy Campaign, October 1976 (Box 22)
    - McClan (?) (Box 22)
    - McConnell, James (psychology professor), October 10, 1975 (Box 22)
    - NcCormack (Ann Arbor councilman), March 31, 1973 (Box 22)
    - McCracken, Paul (economics professor), 1968-1976; 7 envelopes
      - Nixon economic aide, December 6, 1968 (Box 22)
      - October 11, 1971 (Box 22)
      - Foreign Administrative Financial Advisor, January 12, 1972 (Box 22)
      - September 16, 1975 (Box 22)
      - Carter's economic policies, November 23, 1976 (Box 22)
      - "McCracken sitting above Union members who are voting,", undated (Box 22)
      - March 16, 1982 (Box 22)
    - McCullough, Senator (candidate for Governor), February 3, 1978 (Box 22)
    - McDonough, Bob, April 1, 1975 (Box 22)
    - McGovern, George, August 21-23, 1972; undated; 2 envelopes (Box 22)
    - McHale, Barbara (Box 22)
    - McHenry, May 7, 1980 (Box 22)
    - McKoen, Marshall, October 31, 1977 (Box 22)
    - McPherson, Bruce (Superintendent of Education) (Box 22)
    - MacRae, Meredith, February 8, 1974 (Box 22)
    - Madcat Ruth (musicians) (Box 22)
      (See-Lake, Oliver)
    - Maddox, Gilbert, September 16, 1970 (Box 22)
    - Maddox, Lester, October 11, 1971 (Box 22)
    - Madison, Joe (Box 22)
    - Maga (MAGA?), February 20, 1980 (Box 22)
    - Mantels (restaurant), March 29, 1981 (Box 22)
    - Martin, William ("Collins Murders movie producer"), March 22, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Masid, Judy, March 19, 1979 (Box 22)
    - Masks, June 3, 1981 (Box 22)
    - Maude's (restaurant), March 10, 1981 (Box 23)
    - Mauldin, William (cartoonist), March 16, 1978 (Box 23)
    - Maurio (?), Bill (weather forecaster), February 10, 1973 (Box 23)
    - Maux (professor) (Box 23)
    - Mayer, Thomas (Box 23)
    - Mazrui, Ali (professor of political science), September 20, 1977; undated; 3 envelopes (Box 23)
    - Mead, Margaret (anthropologist), February 20, 1974; November 3, 1976; 2 envelopes (Box 23)
    - Means, Russell (Box 23)
      (See-Student Life-Teach-Ins)
    - Medical School graduation (Box 23)
    - Medical School library, November 20, 1980 (Box 23)
    - Medieval Festival (Box 23)
      (See-Morris Dancers)
    - Medlin, William (professor of education), March 12, 1979 (Box 23)
    - Meeropol, Robbie (son of Rosenberg) (Box 23)
    - Mekenev (Russian dissident), November 7, 1978 (Box 23)
    - Melman, November 6, 1977 (Box 23)
    - Merle Norman make-over, February 9, 1982 (Box 23)
    - Meyer, David ("Ultra-man"), February-March, 1982; 2 envelopes (Box 23)
    - Mhlambiso (national African representative to the United Nations), November 11, 1977 (Box 23)
    - Michigan Daily staff, 1979-1982; 14 envelopes (Box 23)
      (See also-Shafie, Robia; Student Leadership Conference
    - Michigan state government, 3 envelopes
      - Assistant Budget Director, March 16, 1981 (Box 23)
      - "Lansing--budget cut story,", October 22, 1981 (Box 23)
      - Jackson prisoner, gubernatorial candidate, February 3, 1982 (Box 23)
    - Michigan Student Assembly, 1979-1982; 9 envelopes (Box 23)
      (See also- names of individual assembly members and candidates
    - Michigan Theater, 1979; undated; 3 envelopes (Box 23)
    - Michigras, February 9, 1980 (Box 23)
    - Mihanovic, M., April 16, 1981 (Box 23)
      (See also-Wedding)
    - Mikva, Abner (Illinois Congressman), February 10, 1978 (Box 23)
    - Milan prison warden, August 1973 (Box 23)
    - Miller (State of Michigan economist), October 30, 1980 (Box 23)
    - Miller, Arthur (writer), November 13 and 16, 1973; 3 envelopes (Box 23)
    - Miller, Chris (Lampoon editor), October 19, 1972 (Box 23)
    - Miller, Ruth, October 11, 1977 (Box 23)
    - Miller, Warren, October 14, 1980 (Box 23)
    - Moveable Feast (restaurant), May 6, 1982 (Box 23)
    - Murelly (?), Maria, October 11, 1977 (Box 23)
    - Milliken, William (Governor), 1970-1981; 7 envelopes (Box 23)
    - Minick (Box 23)
    - Minter, Tom (Box 23)
      (See-Cockrell)
    - Minton, James (map room), October 6, 1978 (Box 23)
    - Mitchell, John (saxophone player), February 1, 1977 (Box 23)
    - Mitchell (city council candidate), January 24, 1978 (Box 23)
    - Mondale, Walter, 1974-1978; 8 envelopes (Box 23)
    - Moniz, Ramsey, February 21, 1974 (Box 23)
    - Moody, Blair (Michigan Supreme Court judge), October 17, 1976 (Box 23)
    - Moore, Sarah (Box 23)
    - Moorehouse (Box 23)
    - Moot Court, March 24, 1982 (Box 23)
    - Morris (professor and Democratic city council candidate), January 12, 1972 (Box 23)
    - Morris, Charles (LSA assistant dean), November 30, 1972; undated; 2 envelopes (Box 23)
    - Morris Dancers (Box 23)
    - Morris, Frank (BGS counselor), September 27, 1972 (Box 23)
    - Motly and Muffins Band (?), March 16, 1981 (Box 23)
    - Mott Childrens Hospital, September 20, 1979 (Box 23)
    - Munson, Richard (Pilot Program), January 18, 1975 (Box 23)
    - Murphy, Rhodes (Box 23)
    - Murray, Sy (city administrator), September 26, 1977; November 23, 1977; 2 envelopes (Box 23)
    - NAACP (Box 23)
    - Nader, Ralph, October 18, 1968; March 1970; 2 envelopes (Box 23)
    - Natow, Nancy (artist) (Box 23)
    - Nelson, Rick, October 23, 1979 (Box 23)
    - Ness, Gayle (Box 23)
    - Neughberzer, Father, November 12, 1967 (Box 23)
    - New York City, November 13, 1979 (Box 23)
    - Newell, Barbara (Vice President for Student Affairs), September 14, 1970 (Box 23)
    - Newton, Huey (Box 23)
    - Nicholls, J. A. (aerospace lab), February 23, 1976 (Box 23)
    - Nichols, Jeanne (public access T.V.), May 11, 1977 (Box 23)
    - Niess, Robert J. (Professor of French) (Box 23)
    - Nin, Anais (Box 23)
    - Nissen, Steve (Box 23)
    - Nixon, Pat (Box 23)
    - Nixon, Richard (in Michigan), April (?) 10, 1974 (Box 23)
    - Norman, Jeff (head of SACUA), May 5, 1971 (Box 23)
    - Norman (professor), October 13, 1978 (Box 23)
    - Nuclear Medicine, November 14, 1979 (Box 23)
    - Nursing (Box 23)
      (See-Hospitals; Petersen, Lowell)
    - Nystuen, John (professor of geography), 1981-1982; 2 envelopes (Box 23)
    - O'Hara, James (Democrat from Michigan), October 28, 1975 (Box 23)
    - Oksenberg, Michel (professor of Chinese), February 9, 1976; January 22, 1976; 2 envelopes (Box 23)
    - Old German (restaurant), 2 envelopes (Box 23)
    - Olympic athletes, February 7, 1980 (Box 23)
    - O'Reilley, September 11, 1980 (Box 23)
    - Organsky, November 27, 1973 (Box 23)
      (See also-Mayer, Thomas)
    - Orientation, August 13, 1981 (Box 23)
    - Otterbacher, John (Michigan Senator), October 17, 1977; 2 envelopes (Box 23)
    - Overburger (Box 23)
    - Owens (professor), January 31, 1978 (Box 23)
    - Owens, Harold (Under Sheriff, 2 envelopes (Box 23)
  - P-S
    - Papadopoulos, Andreos (Greek political leader), March 21, 1974 (Box 23)
    - Pappagalo's (beauty salon), February 9, 1982 (Box 23)
    - Peace Corps, October 14, 1980; 3 envelopes (Box 23)
      (See also-Brown, John
    - Peck (Box 23)
    - Pena, Deagelia (Affirmative Action Director), 1978; 2 envelopes (Box 23)
    - "Percussions" (musicians) (Box 23)
    - Percy, Charles, September 8, 1977 (Box 23)
    - Perez, Shimon (Israeli politician), November 20, 1967 (Box 23)
    - Petersen, Lowell, May 6, 1981 (Box 23)
    - Peterson, Oscar, February 2, 1980 (Box 23)
    - Peyton (singer and guitarist) (Box 23)
    - Phoenix Memorial Laboratory, March 5, 1981 (Box 23)
    - Physical Therapy, 1981; undated; 3 envelopes (Box 23)
    - Pickett, Lee (watch collector, Campus Jewelry), June 1978 (Box 23)
    - Pierce, Ed (Ann Arbor mayor and political activist), April 7, 1975; October 27, 1976; 2 envelopes (Box 23)
    - Pierpont, Wilbur (University Vice President and Chief Financial Officer), May 19, 1971; November 16, 1976; 2 envelopes (Box 23)
    - Pioneer High School pep rally (Box 23)
    - Plamondon, Pun (?), July 31, 1972 (Box 23)
    - Police, June 1, 1981 (Box 23)
    - Polick, Missy (Box 23)
      (See-Trowbridge, Ron)
    - Polish history professor, January 12, 1982 (Box 23)
    - Poole, Margery, June 7, 1979 (Box 23)
    - Porter (Box 23)
    - Postill, Fred, January 15, 1973 (Box 23)
    - Potter, Chris, October 30, 1980 (Box 23)
    - Pound House, June 1, 1981 (Box 23)
    - Power, Philip (candidate for Senate), 1978; undated; 2 envelopes (Box 23)
    - Power, Sarah (Regent), 1974; 1978; 1980; 3 envelopes (Box 23)
    - Pratt, Alexander (academic judiciary), October 30, 1979 (Box 23)
    - Premph (?), David, February 15, 1972 (Box 23)
    - Presidential Security Council, November 11, 1981 (Box 23)
    - Presidential Tea (University of Michigan) (Box 23)
    - Pretonius (South African professor), September 15, 1977 (Box 23)
    - Prison Conference (Box 23)
    - Proffer, Karl (professor, RLT), 1976; undated; 2 envelopes (Box 23)
    - Progressive Student Association, October 24, 1981 (Box 23)
    - Pryor, Richard, and Harvey Keitel ("Blue Collar" Proms), June 1, 1977 (Box 23)
    - Pursell, Carl (United States Congressman), 1976-1978; 4 envelopes
      - Election night, November 2, 1976 (Box 23)